<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 2/28/2015 2:47:03 PM -->
<GameData>

	<Units>
		<Row>
			<Type>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</Type>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_RENAISSANCE_CALC_COWBOY_TEXT</Civilopedia>
			<Strategy>TXT_KEY_UNIT_CALC_COWBOY_STRATEGY</Strategy>
			<Help>TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_COWBOY</Help>
			<Combat>34</Combat>
			<RangedCombat>0</RangedCombat>
			<Cost>200</Cost>
			<!--<FaithCost>450</FaithCost>-->
			<RequiresFaithPurchaseEnabled></RequiresFaithPurchaseEnabled>
			<MoveAfterPurchase>false</MoveAfterPurchase>
			<Moves>3</Moves>
			<BaseSightRange>2</BaseSightRange>
			<Class>UNITCLASS_RIFLEMAN</Class>
			<CombatClass>UNITCOMBAT_GUN</CombatClass>
			<Domain>DOMAIN_LAND</Domain>
			<DefaultUnitAI>UNITAI_DEFENSE</DefaultUnitAI>
			<MilitarySupport>true</MilitarySupport>
			<MilitaryProduction>true</MilitaryProduction>
			<Pillage>true</Pillage>
			
			<!--<IgnoreBuildingDefense>true</IgnoreBuildingDefense>-->
			
			<PrereqTech>TECH_RIFLING</PrereqTech>
			<ObsoleteTech>TECH_REPLACEABLE_PARTS</ObsoleteTech>
			<GoodyHutUpgradeUnitClass>UNITCLASS_GREAT_WAR_INFANTRY</GoodyHutUpgradeUnitClass>
			<AdvancedStartCost>30</AdvancedStartCost>
			<MinAreaSize>-1</MinAreaSize>
			<NukeDamageLevel>-1</NukeDamageLevel>
			<CombatLimit>100</CombatLimit>
			<XPValueAttack>3</XPValueAttack>
			<XPValueDefense>3</XPValueDefense>
			<UnitArtInfo>ART_DEF_UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitArtInfo>
			<MoveRate>QUADRUPED</MoveRate>
			<UnitFlagIconOffset>2</UnitFlagIconOffset>
			<PortraitIndex>2</PortraitIndex>
			<IconAtlas>TX_COLOR_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
			<UnitFlagAtlas>TX_ALPHA_ATLAS</UnitFlagAtlas>
		</Row>
	</Units>

	<Unit_AITypes>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_DEFENSE</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_ATTACK</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_EXPLORE</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_AITypes>

	<Unit_ClassUpgrades>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<UnitClassType>UNITCLASS_GREAT_WAR_INFANTRY</UnitClassType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_ClassUpgrades>
	
	<Unit_FreePromotions>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_NO_DEFENSIVE_BONUSES</PromotionType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_CAN_MOVE_AFTER_ATTACKING</PromotionType>
		</Row>
		<!--<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_CITY_PENALTY</PromotionType>
		</Row>-->
	</Unit_FreePromotions>

	<Unit_Flavors>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_OFFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>10</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_DEFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>10</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<!--<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_MOBILE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>7</Flavor>
		</Row>-->
	</Unit_Flavors>

	<!--<Unit_ResourceQuantityRequirements>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<ResourceType>RESOURCE_HORSE</ResourceType>
			<Cost>1</Cost>
		</Row>
	</Unit_ResourceQuantityRequirements>-->

	<UnitGameplay2DScripts>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_CALC_COWBOY</UnitType>
			<SelectionSound>AS2D_SELECT_CAVALRY</SelectionSound>
			<FirstSelectionSound>AS2D_BIRTH_CAVALRY</FirstSelectionSound>
		</Row>
	</UnitGameplay2DScripts>

	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CALC_COWBOY">
			<Text>Cowboy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_RENAISSANCE_CALC_COWBOY_TEXT">
			<Text>A cowboy is an animal herder who tends cattle on ranches in North America, traditionally on horseback, and often performs a multitude of other ranch-related tasks. The historic American cowboy of the late 19th century arose from the vaquero traditions of northern Mexico and became a figure of special significance and legend. A subtype, called a wrangler, specifically tends the horses used to work cattle. In addition to ranch work, some cowboys work for or participate in rodeos. [NEWLINE] [NEWLINE]In the 18th century, the residents of Spanish Texas began to herd cattle on horseback to sell in Louisiana, both legally and illegally. Their horses were of jennet type which became the Spanish Mustang. By the early 19th century, the Spanish Crown, and later, independent Mexico, offered empresario grants in what would later be Texas to non-citizens, such as settlers from the United States. In 1821, Stephen F. Austin led a group which became the first English-speaking Mexican citizens. Following Texas independence in 1836, even more Americans immigrated into the empresario ranching areas of Texas. Here the settlers were strongly influenced by the Mexican vaquero culture, borrowing vocabulary and attire from their counterparts, but also retaining some of the livestock-handling traditions and culture of the Eastern United States and Great Britain. The Texas cowboy was typically a bachelor who hired on with different outfits from season to season.[NEWLINE] [NEWLINE]Following the American Civil War, vaquero culture combined with the cattle herding and drover traditions of the southeastern United States that evolved as settlers moved west. Additional influences developed out of Texas as cattle trails were created to meet up with the railroad lines of Kansas and Nebraska, in addition to expanding ranching opportunities in the Great Plains and Rocky Mountain Front, east of the Continental Divide. The new settlers required more horses, to be trained faster, and brought a bigger and heavier horse with them. This led to modifications in the bridling and bitting traditions used by the vaquero. Thus, the Texas cowboy tradition arose from a combination of cultural influences, in addition to the need for adaptation to the geography and climate of west Texas and the need to conduct long cattle drives to get animals to market. [NEWLINE] [NEWLINE]en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cowboy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CALC_COWBOY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>A Rifleman replacement, the Cowboy gets +1 [ICON_MOVES]Movement and an additional +1 [ICON_MOVES] Movement when it starts in Texas territory. When garrisoned, the city it's in generates +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1]Happiness and [ICON_CULTURE]Culture. It is significantly more powerful than the musketman, giving the army with the advanced units a big advantage over civs which have not yet upgraded to the new unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_COWBOY">
			<Text>Rifleman replacement for Texas, when garrisoned, the city gets +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1]Happiness ans [ICON_CULTURE]Culture. +1 [ICON_MOVES]Movement when it starts in Texas territory.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
  
</GameData>