<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 7/27/2016 11:16:41 PM -->
<GameData>
  <!-- TODO: Insert table creation example here. -->
 
  <!-- TODO: Insert table data example here.-->
  
  <!-- Enter your Game Data here. -->
	<!-- Adding a new CityState entry. -->
	<MinorCivilizations>
		<Row>
			<Type>MINOR_CIV_LA_PAZ</Type>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_LA_PAZ</Description>
			<ShortDescription>TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_LA_PAZ</ShortDescription>
			<Adjective>TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_LA_PAZ_ADJ</Adjective>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_LA_PAZ_PEDIA</Civilopedia>
			<DefaultPlayerColor>PLAYERCOLOR_MINOR_GREEN</DefaultPlayerColor>
			<ArtDefineTag>ART_DEF_CIVILIZATION_MINOR</ArtDefineTag>
			<ArtStyleType>ARTSTYLE_SOUTH_AMERICA</ArtStyleType>
			<ArtStyleSuffix>_AMER</ArtStyleSuffix>
			<ArtStylePrefix>AMERICAN</ArtStylePrefix>
			<MinorCivTrait>MINOR_TRAIT_CULTURED</MinorCivTrait>
		</Row>
	</MinorCivilizations>
	<MinorCivilization_CityNames>
		<Row>
			<MinorCivType>MINOR_CIV_LA_PAZ</MinorCivType>
			<CityName>TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_LA_PAZ</CityName>
		</Row>
	</MinorCivilization_CityNames>
	<MinorCivilization_Flavors>
		<Row>
			<MinorCivType>MINOR_CIV_LA_PAZ</MinorCivType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_EXPANSION</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>5</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<MinorCivType>MINOR_CIV_LA_PAZ</MinorCivType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_CITY_DEFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>10</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<MinorCivType>MINOR_CIV_LA_PAZ</MinorCivType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_DEFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>0</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<MinorCivType>MINOR_CIV_LA_PAZ</MinorCivType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_WONDER</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>0</Flavor>
		</Row>
	</MinorCivilization_Flavors>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_LA_PAZ">
			<Text>La Paz</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_LA_PAZ_ADJ">
			<Text>La Paz</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_LA_PAZ_PEDIA">
			<Text>The de facto capital of Bolivia, La Paz was founded in 1548 by the Spanish conquistador Captain Alonso de Mendoza at the site of the Inca settlement of Laja as a connecting point between the commercial routes that led from Potosi and Oruro to Lima; the full name of the city was originally Nuestra Senora de La Paz  in commemoration of the restoration of peace following the insurrection of Gonzalo Pizarro and fellow conquistadors against the first viceroy of Peru. The city was later moved to its present location in the valley of Chuquiago Marka. La Paz was under Spanish colonial rule as part of the Viceroyalty of the Rio de la Plata, before Bolivia gained independence. Since its founding, the city was the site of numerous revolts. In 1781, the indigenous leader and independence activist Tupac Katari laid siege to the city for a total of six months, but was finally defeated. In 1809 the Bolivian patriot Pedro Domingo Murillo ignited a revolution for independence, marking the beginning of the Spanish American Wars of Independence, which gained the freedom of South American states in 1821. As the seat of the government of Bolivia, La Paz is the site of the Palacio Quemado, the presidential palace. The constitutional capital of Bolivia, Sucre, retains the judicial power. The city hosts numerous foreign embassies as well as international missions in the country. La Paz is an important political, administrative, economic, and sports center of Bolivia; it generates 25 percent of Bolivia's Gross Domestic Product and serves as the headquarters for numerous Bolivian companies and industries.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>
  
