<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 6/8/2017 9:23:27 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKARRAY">
			<Text>Square Kilometre Array</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKARRAY_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit."[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB] - Stephen Hawking[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SKARRAY_TEXT">
			<Text>The Square Kilometre Array is a large multi radio telescope project aimed to be operational in the early to mid-21st century. Whilst its core sites will be based in South Africa and Australia, twelve countries in total will be involved in its operation with the array planned to extend out to at least 3,000 kilometres across the Southern Hemisphere, which would cover a total area of approximately one square kilometre. It will provide the highest resolution images in all astronomy in the hopes of solving of the greatest mysteries of the universe.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_SKARRAY_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from all featureless tiles (no Forest, Jungle, Marsh, Oasis or Flood Plains) worked in all Cities. Provides a free Observatory in the City in which it is built.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must not be built on Hills.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UCONSTRUCTOR">
			<Text>Universal Constructor</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UCONSTRUCTOR_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"We know the basic principles of molecular machinery will work because they do work."[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB] - K. Eric Drexler[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_UCONSTRUCTOR_TEXT">
			<Text>The Universal Constructor, as known as a Molecular Assembler, is a proposed device able to arrange molecules with atomic precision not unlike a highly advanced 3D printer and could allow mass production of incredibly intricate parts on an unprecedented scale. Whilst purely conceptual and largely explored through science-fiction today, no one has yet discovered an insurmountable problem with the underlying theories.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_UCONSTRUCTOR_HELP">
			<Text>Creates a copy of each type of military land unit you control and places the Unit near the City where the Universal Constructor is built. +30% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building military units in this City.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SDI">
			<Text>Strategic Defense Initiative</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SDI_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"The only winning move is not to play."[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB] - WOPR, WarGames[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SDI_TEXT">
			<Text>The Strategic Defense Initiative, nicknamed "Star Wars", was a proposed defense system intended to protect the United States from attack by nuclear missiles. It was first publicly announced by President Ronald Reagan in 1983 and considered a whole range of methods for intercepting ballistic missiles from orbital lasers to ground-based missile shields. The project was later deemed to be technologically and financially unfeasible and threatened to disrupt the delicate balance of power in the Cold War leading to the program being dissolved in 1993. However, the initiative led to significant advancements in missile defence systems, which are still being developed and deployed to this day.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_SDI_HELP">
			<Text>Reduces population loss from nuclear attack by 25% in all Cities (effect stacks with Bomb Shelters to prevent any loss). Provides a free Bomb Shelter in the City in which it is built.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MARKER_SDI">
			<Text>SDI Marker</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MARKER_SKA">
			<Text>SKA Marker</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>